etribez.com 2014-07-03

# eTribez Privacy Policy

##  [ Privacy Policy](https://www.etribez.com/privacy-policy)

This Privacy Policy Statement (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) explains how eTribez Labs Ltd. (“ **eTribez** ”) may collect, use and may disclose your information and it applies to all use of eTribez’s Website (the “ **Website** ”).

IT IS CLARIFIED THAT ANY USE, COLLECTION AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION PROVIDED BY A USER ENROLLING TO A CAMPAIGN POWERED BY ETRIBEZ IS GOVERENED SOLELY BY THE PRIVACY POLICY PUBLISHED IN SUCH CAMPAIGN AND THIS PRIVECY POLICY DOES NOT APPLY ON IT.

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and review it periodically for the latest information about our privacy practices. By accessing and/or using the Website, you fully agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through the link set forth below.

**The Information We Collect and How We Use it.**

When you interact with the Website we may gather certain information, including the following information:

    *   _Personally Identifiable Information_ – which is information that may identify you in person such as your first and last name, email address, nickname (or other user ID), a password, profession, address, likes and dislikes.

We may collect _Personally Identifiable Information_ that was voluntarily provided by you as part of your interaction with the Website, for example when you contact us for customer service and other support.

We use your _Personally Identifiable Information_ to provide you services, to send communications and administrative emails, and to send marketing messages relating to Website that may be of interest to you. We may do this electronically, for example by email, text or messages through the Website or by telephone or by post.

You may tell us at any time if you do not wish to receive marketing message from us by contacting us at info@etribez.com or by following any instructions we may include in the message we send to you. For example, a STOP message will appear at the foot of marketing text or email messages we send you.

We may retain your _Personal Identifiable Information_ in conformance with applicable laws, to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce the Website Terms of Use, establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Website and take other actions otherwise permitted by law. There may be residual Personal Information that remains within our databases, access logs, and other records.

    * _Non-Personally Identifiable Information_ – which is information that alone cannot identify you including without limitations information derived from Cookies, Pixel Tags and Web Beacons.

We may collect _Non-Personally Identifiable Information_ automatically when you visit the Website, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, and the web page you have visited immediately prior to visiting the Website. This information helps us monitor Website traffic patterns in order to improve our service.

We may use Cookies or similar technology means on the Site. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's web browser while you are viewing a Website. If you elect to block Cookies, you may not be able to access certain personalized sections of our services. We also use log files and Cookies to improve the quality of the Website; to keep track of your login name, passwords, and pages you have visited on the Website.

**Disclosing of any Information to Outside Parties.**

In general we don’t intend to share information provided by you. However, we may share _Personal Identifiable Information_ and _Non-Personally Identifiable Information_ collected via the Website with other companies or individuals as follows: (i) third parties if we have a good faith belief that access, use, or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process or an enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce the applicable Terms of Use of the Website, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of eTribez, its users or the public as required or permitted by law; (ii) any of our subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control with us, in which case we will require them to honor this policy. Additionally, in the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your _Personal and/or Non-Personal Identifiable Information_ may be among the assets transferred (if any); and (iii) third parties to whom you ask us to send Personal and/or Non-Personal Identifiable Information.

If we transfer your information in accordance with condition (i) and (iii) aforementioned, we will make sure that they agree to apply the same levels of protection as we are required to apply to your information and, where appropriate, to use your information strictly in accordance with our instructions.

We will retain information about you after your use of the Website is finished, for as long as permitted for legal, regulatory, fraud and other financial crime prevention and legitimate business purposes.

**Third Party Links** To the extent that the Site contain links or any other information to outside services and resources, We do not control the availability and content of those outside services and resources, and do not control the collection, use or storage of any information about you, including _Personally Identifiable Information_ , by such outside services and resources. Any concerns regarding any such service or resource, or any link thereto, should be directed to such particular service or resource provider.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection**. Protecting the privacy of children and/or minors is very important to us. If we obtain knowledge that a user is under the age of 13, we will take steps to remove that user's _Personally Identifiable Information_ from our databases.

**Security Precautions to Protect your Information**. Standard security safeguards are implemented, including strict access controls, to protect your information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

**Terms and Conditions**. Please also see our Terms of Use published on the Website establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Website.

**Contact Us**. eTribez regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy by contacting us by emailing us at info@etribez.com.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**. We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be effective immediately upon posting on our Website or any other way of notification eTribez will choose at its sole discretion. Since this Privacy Policy may change from time to time, you should check back periodically so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we may be entitled disclose it. By using any part of Website after any such change of this Privacy Policy, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us as outlined herein and in the amended policy.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on: December 31, 2013.
